[
    {
        "front": "あつい",
        "back": "Hot (For Weather)",
        "chapter": "N5 C5"
    },
    {
        "front": "あたたかい",
        "back": "Hot (For Object)",
        "chapter": "N5 C5"
    },
    {
        "front": "つめたい",
        "back": "Cold (For Objects)",
        "chapter": "N5 C5"
    },
    {
        "front": "さむい",
        "back": "Cold (For Weather)",
        "chapter": "N5 C5"
    },
    {
        "front": "きびしい",
        "back": "Strict",
        "chapter": "N5 C5"
    },
    {
        "front": "たかい",
        "back": "Expensive, Tall",
        "chapter": "N5 C5"
    },
    {
        "front": "やすい",
        "back": "Inexpensive, Cheap",
        "chapter": "N5 C5"
    },
    {
        "front": "むずかしい",
        "back": "Difficult",
        "chapter": "N5 C5"
    },
    {
        "front": "やさしい",
        "back": "Easy, Kind, Gentle",
        "chapter": "N5 C5"
    },
    {
        "front": "おもしろい",
        "back": "Interesting",
        "chapter": "N5 C5"
    },
    {
        "front": "はやい",
        "back": "Fast, Quick",
        "chapter": "N5 C5"
    },
    {
        "front": "おそい",
        "back": "Slow",
        "chapter": "N5 C5"
    },
    {
        "front": "いい",
        "back": "Good",
        "chapter": "N5 C5"
    },
    {
        "front": "よくない",
        "back": "Not Good",
        "chapter": "N5 C5"
    },
    {
        "front": "おいしい",
        "back": "Tasty",
        "chapter": "N5 C5"
    },
    {
        "front": "すくない",
        "back": "Little",
        "chapter": "N5 C5"
    },
    {
        "front": "とても",
        "back": "Very",
        "chapter": "N5 C5"
    },
    {
        "front": "くに",
        "back": "Country",
        "chapter": "N5 C5"
    },
    {
        "front": "いつも",
        "back": "Always",
        "chapter": "N5 C5"
    },
    {
        "front": "にほんご",
        "back": "Japanese Language",
        "chapter": "N5 C5"
    },
    {
        "front": "えいご",
        "back": "English",
        "chapter": "N5 C5"
    },
    {
        "front": "りょうり",
        "back": "Dish, food, cuisine",
        "chapter": "N5 C5"
    },
    {
        "front": "コーヒー",
        "back": "Coffee",
        "chapter": "N5 C5"
    },
    {
        "front": "あたらしい",
        "back": "New",
        "chapter": "N5 C5"
    },
    {
        "front": "ふるい",
        "back": "Old (things)",
        "chapter": "N5 C5"
    },
    {
        "front": "いそがしい",
        "back": "Busy",
        "chapter": "N5 C5"
    },
    {
        "front": "たのしい",
        "back": "Enjoyable",
        "chapter": "N5 C5"
    },
    {
        "front": "おおきい",
        "back": "Big",
        "chapter": "N5 C5"
    },
    {
        "front": "ちいさい",
        "back": "Small",
        "chapter": "N5 C5"
    },
    {
        "front": "ひくい",
        "back": "Low",
        "chapter": "N5 C5"
    },
    {
        "front": "わるい",
        "back": "Bad",
        "chapter": "N5 C5"
    },
    {
        "front": "どっな",
        "back": "What kind of",
        "chapter": "N5 C5"
    },
    {
        "front": "どうも",
        "back": "Thanks (informal)",
        "chapter": "N5 C5"
    }
]